Guide to the Hans Reichenbach Papers, 1884-1972 ASP.1973.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, Drawings, Manuscripts, Notebooks, and Photographs, 1884-1952; III.
  - Photographs, Clippings, Proofs, 1909-1979; 17.
    - Photos: Reichenbach, Family & Friends, Portraits of HR, 1912-1948 (Box 42, Folder 1a)
    - Photos: Reichenbach, Family and Friends (Box 42, Folder 1b)
    - Clippings, 1945-1951 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Photos of Reichenbach (Various Ages), 1917, 1925, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Photos: Reichenbach's Portrait and Landscapes (Various Ages) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Photos: Reichenbach (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Photos: Landscapes (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Photos: Landscapes and Portraits (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - H. Reichenbach's Selected Writings - Part One, Proofs, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - H. Reichenbach's Selected Writings: Editor's Proof, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - H. Reichenbach: Selected Writings, Editor's Proof and Letters, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Notes and Drafts, 1911-1973; 18.
    - Hans, Biography and Photo, 1917-1977 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - H.R. Handwritten Notes, 1915, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - H.R. Handwritten Notes (with Letter from Maria Reichenbach), 1915-1918, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3a)
    - H.R. Handwritten Notes (Box 44, Folder 3b)
    - H.R. Handwritten Notes (Box 44, Folder 3c)
    - H.R. Theory of Series and Gödels Theorem (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Letters (with Family Tree), 1918-1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - H.R. Unpublished Manuscripts (and Letters from Maria Reichenbach), 1915-1927, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Abraham Kaplan: In Memoriam (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - H.R. Letters to Bertrand Russell and Original Manuscript, 1940-1971 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - De Broglie Paper: The Philosophical Significance of the Duality of Waves and Corpuscles - Original in English, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes, (Part I-VI), 1951 and 1959; 19.
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part I, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part II, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part III, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part IV, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part V, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - The Use of Mathematical Models in the Measurement of Attitudes - Part VI, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Hans Reichenbach Bibliography from Routledge, Modern Philosophy of Science (ditto Master incl.), 1959 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Reichenbach - Ditto Masters - Bibliography, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Supplementary Material, 20.
    The documents in this subseries were acquired after the initial aquistion of the Reichenbach Papers, mostly by donation or exchange of photocopies with other repositories. In some cases, a note about the provenance of the material is included at the beginning of the folder.
    - H. Reichenbach, Theory of Series & Gödel's Theorem (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Reichenbach to Joself Petzoldt, 1922-1923 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Notes and Correspondence between Reichenbach and Bertrand Russell, 1923-1958 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Reichenbach's Logic Tests, 1942-1984 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Book List of the Hans Reichenbach Collection, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Name Index, IV.
  The name index lists personal names of individual as they appear in the papers in alphabetic order according to last name. First, the index notes the box and folder number, and the item count lists how many times this specific individual is mentioned in each folder.
  - Abelspies, J.R. Carlos (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Abrahanson-Baer, Fran Lili (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Achinstein, Peter (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Adler, Alfred (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Adler, Arthur (Box 14, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Adler, Friedrich (Box 15, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Ajdulkiewiez, Kasimir (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Ajdulkiewiez, Kasimir (Box 13, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - Alexander, W.H. (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Allen, Bennet H. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Allen, Edward S. (Box 13, Folder 39, Item 6)
  - Allen, Edward S. (Box 14, Folder 43, Item 5)
  - Allen, Edward S. (Box 25, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Allen, Edward S. (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Allen, George (Box 13, Folder 39, Item 5)
  - Allen, George (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Alvarez de Toledo, Marquis (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Ambruster, Dr. L (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Amiri, Mafalda (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Anderson, Luther (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Appleman, Matt (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Archer, H. (Box 36, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Asher, Rolland (Box 37-2, Folder unknown container, Item 2)
  - Ashton, Geoffrey (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 13, Folder 39, Item 24)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 14, Folder 43, Item 5)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 15, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 16, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Aster, Ernst (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Audoin, Charles (Box 16, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Axster, Ilse (Box 14, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Bachem, A. (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 3)
  - Balet, L., (1) (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Banet, Leo (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Banet, Leo (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Barata, Joseph G. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Bargmann, Valentin (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 7)
  - Bargmann, Valentin (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Bargmann, Valentin (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 3)
  - Bargmann, Valentin (Box 18, Folder 22, Item 28)
  - Bargmann, Valentin (Box 23, Folder 27, Item 12)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Barth, J. Ambrosius (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Bass, Robert (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Bass, Robert (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Bates, Roy C. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Bauch, Bruno (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Bauer, Franz (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 4)
  - Baumgart, David (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Baumgart, David (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Baumgartel, Elise (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Bavink, Dr. B. (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Bavink, Dr. B. (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Bavink, Dr. B., (8) (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 8)
  - Bavink, Dr. B. (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bechman, J. Frederick (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Beck, Friedrich (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Beck, Gunther (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Beck, M. (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Becker, Albrecht (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Becker, Albrecht (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Becker, Albrecht (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 5)
  - Becker, Albrecht (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Becker, Friedrich (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Becker, Oskar (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Becker, Oskar (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Becker, Oskar (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Becker, Oskar (Box 25, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Behmann, H. (Box 16, Folder 27, Item 4)
  - Behrens, M. (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Bell, Lamar A. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Benary, Dr. W. (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 5)
  - Benary, Dr. W. (Box 16, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Benary, Dr. W. (Box 16, Folder 1, Item 14)
  - Benjamin, Walter (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Benjamin, Walter (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Bennet, Howard (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Bennet, T. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Benrubi, J. (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Bense, Max (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Berghoben, M. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Bergmann, Gustav (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Beringuier, R. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Berliner, A. (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Berliner, A. (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 3)
  - Berliner, A. (Box 13, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Berliner, A. (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 42)
  - Berliner, A. (Box 16, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 16, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Bernfield, Siegfried (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Bernfield, Siegfried (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Bernfeld, Suzanne (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Berr, K. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Bernstein, Felix (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Bertalanffy, Ludwig von (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Bertalanffy, Ludwig von (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 10)
  - Bertalanffy, Ludwig von (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Bertling, K.O. (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Beth, E. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - Bertholet, Marcelin (Box 26, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Bettauer, Gunther (Box 23, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Bidwell, Charles (Box 28, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Bieberbach, Ludwig (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Bigelow, Karl W. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Biggins, Albert J. (Box 36, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Bilge, Cemil (Box 37, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Bilherz, A. (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Birnbaum, Allan (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Bisbee, Eleanor (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 10)
  - Bisbee, Eleanor (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Black, Max (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Black, Max (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Blackwell, Kenneth (Box 44, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 37, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Adolf (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Pfarrer (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Bloch, Werner (Box 37, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Blum, H.F. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Blum, H.F. (Box 37, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Blume, H (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 4)
  - Blumenfeld, Walter (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Blumenfeld, Walter (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Blumenfeld, Walter (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Boas, George (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 4)
  - Bochenski, J.M. (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Bohm, C.R. (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Böhme, Eberhard (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bohr, Niels (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Boll, Marcel (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Boll, Marcel (Box 14, Folder 44, Item 18)
  - Bon, Fred (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Bonetti, Paolo (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Boodin, John E. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Born, Max (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Born, Max (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Bornstein, E. (Box 14, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Bertolotti, Enea (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Bosel, S. (Box 16, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Bostain, Mary (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 12)
  - Bothe, Walter (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Boyce, Joseph C. (Box 38, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Brackman, A. (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Braithwaite, R.B. (Box 13, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Branca, Prof. (Box 15, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Branch, J.H. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Brand-Maher, C.E. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 12)
  - Brandt, Karl (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Brandt, Richard (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Braubach, B. (Box 16, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Braun, F. (Box 14, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Braziller, George (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Braziller, George (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Braziller, George (Box 37, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - Breuer, Joseph (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Brieger, F. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Britzel, Hans (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Britzelmay, Wilhelm (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Britzelmay, Wilhelm (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Broad, C.D. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Brockhaus, F.A. (Box 15, Folder 49, Item 2)
  - Brod, Max (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - de Broglie, Louis (Box 13, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - de Broglie, Louis (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - von Bronsart, H. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - Bronstein, Daniel J. (Box 13, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Bronstein, Daniel J. (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Bronstein, Daniel J. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Brown, Arthur Robert (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Brubachter, John S. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Brubaum, Karl (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Bruning, Walther (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Brunswik, Egon (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 9)
  - Brunschwieg, Leon (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Bubi (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 3)
  - Buck, Roger (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Budzislawski, Hermann (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Burhoe, Ralph W. (Box 18, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Burkamp, Wilhem (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Burks, Arthur (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Burns, Jim (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Burstyn, W. (Box 13, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Bush, Vannevar (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Campos, N. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Capuano, I (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Caratheodory, Constantine (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Caratheodory, Constantine (Box 16, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 60)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 18)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 14, Folder 23, Item 4)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 19)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 15, Folder 27, Item 10)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 15, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 15, Folder 50, Item 5)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 16, Folder 28, Item 10)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 5)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 25, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 26, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 37, Folder 17, Item 54)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Rudolf (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Carnap, Hanna Thost (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Carson, Shirley M. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Carter, Mark B. (Box 41, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Carthaus, Vilma (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Carthaus, Vilma (Box 44, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Carthaus, Vilma (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cassirer, Eva (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 23, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 3)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 15, Folder 27, Item 6)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 15, Folder 50, Item 3)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 16, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 25, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Castell, Alburey (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Cavazza, Fabio Luca (Box 37, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Ceccate, Silvio (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Chari, C.T.K. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Chari, Krishnama (Box 13, Folder 19, Item 2)
  - Chatelet, A. (Box 37, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Cheng, Ping Pi (Box 14, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Chevassus, R. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Chia, Tang Lu (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Chisholm, Roderick (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 14)
  - Chisholm, Roderick (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Churchman, C. West (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - Churchman, C. West (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Clay, J. (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Clay, J. (Box 14, Folder 45, Item 18)
  - Clay, J. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Clemens, Cyril (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Coffa, Alberto (Box 41, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Coffman, L. Dale (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Collins, Lester (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Colligan, Francis J. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Collignon, Arthur (Box 14, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Colver, Wayne (Box 38, Folder unknown container, Item 13)
  - Courant, Richard (Box 14, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Courant, Richard (Box 14, Folder 45, Item 3)
  - Copeland, Arthur & Dorothy (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Copeland, A.E. (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Copeland, A.E. (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Cornelius, H. (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 10)
  - Cornelius, H. (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Cornelius, H. (Box 14, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Cornelius, H. (Box 16, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cornicelius, Max (Box 15, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Cohen, J.M. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Box 41, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Box 42, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Cohn, Jonas (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Copi, Irving (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Cowles, Alfred (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Creed, Isabel (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Creed, Isabel (Box 40, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Cremer, M. (Box 15, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Crombie, A.C. (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Crudeli, Umberto (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Cruz, Fernando (Box 18, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Curry, Haskel B. (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Curry, Haskel B. (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Dahmen, Dr. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Dalkey, Norman (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 4)
  - Dane, Albert E. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Dane, Albert E. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Dantzig, D. van (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Dermois, G. (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Daus, Paul H. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Phillip (Box 38, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Davis, Alice (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Debe, Arno (Box 15, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Defant, A. (Box 14, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Delaere, Georges (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 4)
  - Della Valle, Guido (Box 16, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - De Finetti, Bruno (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Dempster, A.J. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Demuth, Dr. (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Dennes, William R. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - Deri, Hubert B. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - DeSaussure, Frank (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Dessoir, Max (Box 14, Folder 24, Item 5)
  - Dessoir, Max (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Dessoir, Max (Box 15, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Destouches, M.J.L. (Box 37, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Destouches, M.J.L. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 7)
  - Dexter, Lewis A. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Deutsch, Leonard (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Dewey, John (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Dick, Phillip K. (Box 38, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Dik, M. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Diemer, Alwin (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 3)
  - Dincerin, Bay Hamit (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Dingle, Herbert (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Dingle, Herbert (Box 13, Folder 7, Item 10)
  - Dingle, Herbert (Box 16, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Dieck, W. (Box 14, Folder 47, Item 6)
  - Dilworth, Nelson S. (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Dingilian, David H. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Dirac, P.A. (Box 40, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Dodd, Paul (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Dodd, E. L. (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Dodd, E. L. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Doetsch, G. (Box 16, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Dorge, Karl (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Dorge, Karl (Box 14, Folder 46, Item 6)
  - Dorge, Karl (Box 13, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Dorge, Karl (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Dorner, A. (Box 14, Folder 24, Item 3)
  - Dohnr, R. (Box 13, Folder 11, Item 11)
  - Dohnr, R. (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 2)
  - Dornbusch, Theodor (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Drake, Lucille (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Drake, Stillman (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 6)
  - Dreyfuss, Andre (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Driesch, Hans (Box 13, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Driesch, Hans (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Driesch, Hans (Box 15, Folder 51, Item 4)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 13, Folder 9, Item 7)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 13, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 15, Folder 28, Item 3)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Ducasse, C.J. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 5)
  - Ducasse, C.J. (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Dukas, Helen (Box 37, Folder 20, Item 7)
  - Durr, Karl (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Duse, Emil (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Dykstra, C.A. (Box 18, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Dykstra, C.A. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 6)
  - Ebba, Sundberg (Box 38, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Ebbersole, Kranl B. (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Ecco, Humberto (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - Eck, Hans van (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Edwards, Paul (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Ehmert, A. (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Ehrenfest, P. (Box 14, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Ehrenfest, T. (Box 15, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Frau Prof. (Box 13, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 13, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 13, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 14, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 14, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 15, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 16, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 25, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 28, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Einstein, Otto (Box 14, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Otto (Box 15, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Ellis, J. W. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Ellison, William H. (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Engelhard, Viktor (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Epling, Carl (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - Epstein, J. (Box 15, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Epstein, Paul (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Erasmus, Charles (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Erichson, W. (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Espinoza, J. Manuel (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Ewald, P. (Box 14, Folder 25, Item 5)
  - Ewald, P. (Box 15, Folder 29, Item 3)
  - Ewald, P. (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Falk, Raymund (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Farber, Marvin (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Fechner, Albert (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Feigl, Herbert (Box 13, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Feigl, Herbert (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Feigl, Herbert (Box 15, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Feigl, Herbert (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Feigl, Herbert (Box 37, Folder 23, Item 119)
  - Feinberg, Barry (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Ferrier, J. (Box 37, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Feynman, R.P. (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Filippi, M. Ulysse (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Filippi, M. Ulysse (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Fischer, Adolf (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Fischer, Eugen (Box 15, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Fischer, Gustav (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Fischer, Herbert (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Fischer, Hugo (Box 14, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Fischer, S. (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Fladt, ? (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Fleischlauer, Otto (Box 25, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Forsythe, George E. (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Foubes, Joseph (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Franck, J. (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Franco, Jerry (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Frank, Felix (Box 13, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 13, Folder 12, Item 7)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 3)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 19)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 14, Folder 26, Item 7)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 14)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 15, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 18, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 18, Folder 34, Item 3)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 18, Folder 35, Item 6)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 37, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Frank, Phillip (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Frankel, Adolf (Box 13, Folder 12, Item 11)
  - Frankel, Adolf (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Frankel, Adolf (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Frankel, Adolf (Box 14, Folder 26, Item 5)
  - Frankel, Adolf (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Franklin-Tarsulat (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 3)
  - Fraser, R.G.J. (Box 37, Folder 2, Item 1)